readthehook.com 2006-12-29

# The Privacy Policyin the Hook newspaper of Charlottesville

>> Back to The HooK front page  

The Hook values your privacy. We will not request any personally identifying information from you in order to visit our website.

The website contains many hyperlinks to advertisers and to other sites we believe you'll find useful and convenient. However, such non-Hook websites may have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we cannot take responsibility or assume liability for their policies or actions.

We will post any substantial changes in this privacy policy at least 30 days prior to the change taking effect. Any information collected under this current policy will remain bound by the terms of this privacy policy. After the changes take effect, all new information collected, if any, will be subject to the revised privacy policy.

Any transmission that you make on the Internet-- such as sending an email-- is not secure. For instance, when you place a classified ad, enter a contest, buy a product, or send us an e-mail, that information could be intercepted by hackers. Moreover, while all information is stored securely, there is always a risk that a hacker will gain entrance to the servers where your information is kept. The Hook is not responsible for accidental loss or theft of your personal information.

The Hook uses outside service providers for some of our Web site services-- including, but not limited to-- electronic personal ads. We do not control their privacy policies.

While our site's statistical tracking software monitors IP addresses and referring URLs, along with other information about what you view on the site, we do not collect individual information out of these logs. We use the _general_ statistical information to help us understand how users view our site.

Information we gather will not be sold, lent, rented, or otherwise shown to advertisers or third-party vendors.

The Hook does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, although we have no way of knowing if a child is posing as an adult. We ask for parents to fill in any online contests or registrations aimed at children.

NEW: We also operate a related site, a news blog filled with lots of user comments. This related site asks users for their name and email address in case a comment is questioned or challenged. This related site is called theHook.net, and the comments are not verified or necessarily supported by the journalists at the Hook.

For questions or comments, contact the editor, Hawes Spencer, editor@readthehook.com.

#

>> Back to The HooK front page
